A Guide to the Papers of the Low Moor Iron Company
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Bound Volumes
  - Accounts
    - D. Store Accounts: 2. Stores-Daybook; most detail items purchased, 1881-1920; 17 volumes
    - D. Store Accounts: 3. Stores-Journals; workers accounts, 1891-1924; 11 volumes
  - Annual Reports
    - A. Pig Iron Production; letters, 1904-1907; 1 volume
  - Banking
    - A. General, 1881-1896; 3 volumes
    - B. Nassau National Bank of Brooklyn; Low Moor accounts, 1893-1898; 3 volumes
    - C. National Bank of Commerce, New York; accounts and collections, 1879-1896; 3 volumes
  - Bills
    - A. Bills payable, 1882-1916; 7 volumes
    - B. Bills received, 1894-1926; 29 volumes
  - Boarding House Books
    - A. General, 1916-1920; 3 volumes
  - Cashbooks
    - A. General; numbered sequence, 1873-1925; 11 volumes
    - B. Cashbooks, Miscellaneous, 1879-1923; 6 volumes
    - C. Petty Cash, 1879-1925; 11 volumes
  - Check Stub
    - A. Corn Exchange Bank of New York, 1904-1915; 3 volumes
    - B. National Bank of Commerce, 1879-1895; 7 volumes
    - C. Miscellaneous; numbered sequence of stubs; bank not indicated, 1890-1915; 5 volumes
  - Coal
    - A. Coal Mined, Hauled, and Delivered, 1886-1916; 4 volumes
    - B. Coal Orders; numbered sequence, 2, 3, and [4], 1904-1921; 3 volumes
    - C. Coal Sales, 1904-1919; 5 volumes
  - Indices
    - A. Unidentified indices to unidentified volumes, 15 volumes
  - Inventories
    - A. Store #1-Low Moor; records of semi-annual inventories, 1907-1917; 9 volumes
    - B. Store #2, 1906-1917; 10 volumes
    - C. Store #3, 1907, 1916; 2 volumes
    - D. Store #4, 1906-1908; 4 volumes
    - E. Store #5, 1904-1916; 15 volumes
    - F. Store #7, 1904-1916; 15 volumes
    - G. Store #8, 1904-1916; 15 volumes
    - H. Store #9-Kay Moor, 1906-1925; 17 volumes
    - I. Store #10-S. Fayette, 1904-1914; 10 volumes
    - J. Store #11-Kay Moor, 1906-1916; 11 volumes
    - K. Store #12-Fayetteville, 1910-1924; 7 volumes
    - L. Warehouse, 1906-1917; 9 volumes
    - M. Miscellaneous; includes Fenwick Mine, dynamite, stores, 1900-1912; 12 volumes
  - Invoices
    - A. General, 1875-1889; 7 volumes
  - Iron, Ore & Pig
    - A. Contracts, 1903-1919; 13 volumes; numbered sequence, 2-12
    - B. Miscellaneous; includes an iron weight book; ore hauled; ore on hand, etc., 1888-1899; 6 volumes
    - C. Produced/shipped; includes a ledger for Furnace C, and one for Covington; sequence labeled "Iron Ledger" and numbered 1-3, 1881-1907, 1880-1916; 8 volumes
    - D. Sales; includes some agents' letter, and a "kicker" book of complaints, 1883-1912; 8 volumes
    - E. Shipments-General, 1883-1920; 24 volumes
    - F. Shipments-Covington Furnace, 1895-1918; 8 volumes
    - G. Shipments-Low Moor Furnaces, 1877-1918; 9 volumes
  - Journals
    - A. General, 1880-1916; 3 volumes
    - B. Numbered Sequence; #1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 1879-1924; 5 volumes
    - C. Lettered Sequence; [A]-D, C, ED, E, 1873-1895; 7 volumes
    - D. Stack Mines; B-D, 1881-1889; 3 volumes
    - E. Store, 1883-1911; 3 volumes
    - F. Transfer, 1901; 1910-1923; 3 volumes
  - Ledgers
    - A. General, 1873-1899; 6 volumes
    - B. Audit, 1881-1902; 6 volumes and 5 index volumes
    - C. Claims, 1919, 1920, 1924; 2 volumes
    - D. Hands, 1873-1881; 7 volumes
    - E. Lettered Sequence, 1873-1901; 5 volumes
    - F. Stack Mine; volumes B and D of lettered sequence, 1882-1889; 2 volumes
  - Letter Books
    - A. Agent; includes letters of Asa Snyder, John N. Gordon, and Thomas A. Mack, 1883-1886; 4 volumes
    - B. Numbered Sequence; #1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 1879-1924; 5 volumes
    - C. Lettered Sequence; [A]-D, C, ED, E, 1873-1895; 7 volumes
    - D. Stack Mines; B-D, 1881-1889; 3 volumes
    - E. Store, 1883-1911; 3 volumes
    - F. Transfer, 1901; 1910-1923; 3 volumes
  - Ledgers
    - A. General, 1873-1899; 6 volumes
    - B. Audit, 1881-1902; 6 volumes and 5 index volumes
    - C. Claims, 1919, 1920, 1924; 2 volumes
    - D. Hands, 1873-1881; 7 volumes
    - E. Lettered Sequence, 1873-1901; 5 volumes
    - F. Stack Mine; volumes B and D. of lettered sequence, 1882-1889; 2 volumes
  - Letter Books
    - A. Agent; includes letters of Asa Snyder, John N. Gordon, and Thomas A. Mack, 1883-1886; 4 volumes
    - B. Alleghany Iron Mountain Mining Company; John Ham, superintendent, 1889-1893; 2 volumes
    - C. Dolly Ann Mine; John Ham, superintendent, 1883-1895; 6 volumes
    - D. Assistant General Manager; E. B. Wilkinson, 1909-1911; 12 volumes
    - E. General Manager; H. G. Merry, E. C. Means, J. P. Guernsey, F. U. Humbert. Also includes letters of H. M. Goodwin, managing director; and S. G. Cargill, assistant treasurer, 1884-1915; 52 volumes
    - F. Jordan Mines, 1902-1916; 3 volumes
    - G. Low Moor Mines, 1893-1894; 1 volume
    - H. Miscellaneous; includes letters of J. F. Fowle, of the Furnace Department, minutes of the Desotat Mining and Exploring Association for Michigan and Wisconsin mineral development, the Michigan Company, Low Moor Furnace Store; and C & O railroad claims and bills, 1881-1916; 14 volumes
    - I. Pig Iron Shipments, 1882-1927; 8 volumes
    - J. Shipments, 1921-1925; 6 volumes
    - K. Stack Mine, 1888-1893; 7 volumes
    - L. Telegrams, 1902-1915; 6 volumes
    - M. Assistant Treasurer; S. G. Cargill, 1900-1915; 11 volumes
    - N. Treasurer; incoming and outgoing letters of E. A. Low, including letters of Thomas A. Mack, John E. Winslow, H. W. Goodwin, E. D. Wickes, and J. N. Gordon, and of Dalton and Doyle, 1873-1891; 21 volumes
  - Miscellaneous
    - A. Alphabetical sequence; includes records of castings and weights, financial statements of various companies, expenses of the [Low Moor?] medical department, mill silvery records, World War I workers exemption from [draft?] records, slag weights, stock transactions, and tools rented, 1881-1918; 9 volumes
    - B. Chronological sequence, including accounts and other records, not presently identified, 1881-1925; 13 volumes
  - Order Books
    - A. Records of orders and shipments, 1883-1913; 27 volumes
  - Operations-Furnaces
    - A. Low Moor Furnace-Stock Reports & Daily Operations, 1880-1923; 6 volumes
    - B. Miscellaneous; includes production records, accounts, iron and coke use records, orders, pig iron analysis, blast records, and sintering plant records, 1880-1925; 13 volumes
  - Payroll Books
    - A. Low Moor Payrolls; incomplete numbered series, 5, 6, 6, 10-12, 12, 13-15, 1897-1924; 10 volumes
    - B. Furnaces; includes scattered records of furnaces B, C, 3, 4, 6, 1883-1917; 8 volumes
    - C. Mines; includes records of Iron Mtn, Fenwick, Jackson, Jordan, Rich Patch, Rumsey, Strolia, and numbered mines, 1881-1925; 11 volumes
    - D. Dolly Ann Mines, 1885-1921; 5 volumes
    - E. Kay Moor Mines, 1915-1925; 4 volumes
    - F. Stack Mines, 1881-1909; 5 volumes
    - G. Miscellaneous; includes one volume of Covington records, 1880-1920; 13 volumes
  - Railroads
    - Miscellaneous; includes operations credits and debits, freight rates, and a yard record, 1902-1926; 3 volumes
  - Rent Books
    - Records of workers rent payments for living quarters, 1910-1924; 6 volumes
  - Scrapbooks
    - Miscellaneous, scrapbook of newspaper articles re Va. gubernatorial election, 1881; 1 volume
    - Miscellaneous, re financial matters and pig iron, 1887-1890; 1 volumes
  - Scrip Books
    - A. General, 1881-1922; 17 volumes
    - B. Furnaces; includes numbered series, 1-7, 1881-1917; 10 volumes
    - C. Covington, 1898-1902; 1920-1925; 3 volumes
    - D. Low Moor; includes portion of numbered sequence, volumes, 8-18, 20, 22, 24, 26, 27, 1879-1923; 16 volumes
    - E. Mines; includes portion of numbered sequence, volumes, [1],-3, 1-10, 1876-1903; 15 volumes
    - F. Dolly Ann Mines; includes portion of numbered series, volumes [1]-7, 9, 1893-1921; 9 volumes
    - G. Fenwick Mine; volumes 2-4 of numbered series, 1901-1909; 3 volumes
    - H. Iron Mountain Mine; volumes [1], 2, 1893-1901; 2 volumes
    - I. Jackson and Kay Moor Mines: Jackson, 1907-1910; 1 volume
    - I. Jackson and Kay Moor Mines: Kay Moor, 1923-1925; 1 volume
    - J. Jordan Mine, 1900-1925; 5 volumes
    - K. Rumsey Mines, 1899-1906; 3 volumes
    - L. Stack Mines, [1]-4, 1893-1909; 4 volumes
  - Shipments-Incoming
    - A. Coal and Coke Receipts, [1]-[10], 1880-1910; 9 volumes
    - B. Furnace Stock Receipts, 2-[9], 1881-1898; 9 volumes
    - C. Covington Stock Receipts, 3-5, 1901-1914; 3 volumes
    - D. Furnace C Stock Receipts, 1-5, 1895-1914; 6 volumes
    - E. Low Moor Stock Receipts, 10, 11, 13-15, 1898-1915; 5 volumes
  - Shipments-Outgoing
    - A. General, 1893-1920; 9 volumes
    - B. Coal and Coke-Kay Moor, 1-4, 1900-1926; 5 volumes
    - C. Ore Shipments; includes Dolly Ann and Stack mines, 1875-1915; 6 volumes
  - Time Books
    - A. General; many show occupation, daily rate, hours, 1875-1926; 66 volumes
    - B. Callison Mine, 1921 Jun., July; 1 volume
    - C. Coke, 1915, 1916, 1920, 1921; 6 volumes
    - D. Covington, 1901-1925; 6 volumes
    - E. Dolly Ann Mines, 1885-1921; 6 volumes
    - F. Fenwick Mines, 1900-1909; 2 volumes
    - G. Foremen's; includes foremen E. Bateman, P. H. McKinney, F. M. Turner, W. O. Fridley, George K. Anderson, Jr., Mr. Hepler, Floyd Paxton, C. C. Weikel, and J. F. Dillard, 1881-1926; 16 volumes
    - H. Furnace C, 1, 2, t, [6], 1895-1914; 4 volumes
    - I. Furnace, 1880-1926; 19 volumes
    - J. Furnace Repairs, 1919-1922; 7 volumes
    - K. Horse Mountain Mine, 1906-1911; 14 volumes
    - L. Iron Mountain & Jackson Mines: Iron Mountain, 1893-1898; 1 volume
    - L. Iron Mountain & Jackson Mines: Jackson, 1907-1911; 1 volume
    - M. Jordan Mines, 1911-1925; 2 volumes
    - N. Kay Moor Mines, 1916-1925; 3 volumes
    - O. Limestone, 1916 Apr.-June; 2 volumes
    - P. Low Moor; includes a portion of a numbered series, 8, 10-12, 12, 13-16, [7], 18, 1877-1923; 13 volumes
    - Q. Mines; includes portion of a numbered series, 3-7, 1881-1903; 5 volumes
    - R. Rich Patch & Rumsey Mines: Rich Patch, 1916-1925; 3 volumes
    - R. Rich Patch & Rumsey Mines: Rumsey, 1899-1906; 1 volume
    - S. Special. Arranged in alphabetical order. Includes time records of the following: Allegheny Iron Mountain Mining Company, Exyra Time, Low Moor Club - Mrs. H. D. Hitchens, Low Moor Theater - J. A. Hibbert, Night Time Book, Mrs. Norcross Office Time Book, Workers' Daily Production Records, Prospecting, Railroad Maintenance, Shops, Surface, and Washer, 1886-1926; 14 volumes
    - T. Stack Mines; includes several volumes of a numbered sequence, 2, 3, 7, 1883-1901; 6 volumes
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: a. 9B, 1908-1909; 6 volumes
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: b. 10B, 1910-1911; 13 volumes
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: c. 11A, 1907; 2 volumes
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: d. 11B, 1916-1919; 29 volumes
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: e. 12, 1913 Aug.; 1 volume
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: f. 12A, 1910-1913; 7 volumes
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: g. 13A, 1913, 1915; 4 volumes
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: h. 14 A, 1919, 1920; 10 volumes
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: i. 15A, 1920-1921; 5 volumes
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: j. 16A, 1922, 1923; 4 volumes
    - U. Numbered Blast Furnaces: k. 17C, 1925 April; 1 volume
  - Workers-Indices
    - General, 1908-1911, 1918-1925; 8 volumes
- Records
  - Correspondence from E. C. Means, S. G. Cargill, A. H. Reed to G. T. Wickes, 1906 Sept. -1907 Nov. (Box Box 3)
  - Correspondence from S. F. Mays and P. H. McNulty to G. T. Wickes - manager of the mines, 1906 Jan. -1907 Oct. (Box Box 3)
  - F. M. Turner to G. T. Wickes, 1906 Jan. -1907 Feb. (Box Box 3)
  - B. J. Shirkey and R. L. Montieth to G. T Wickes, 1906 June -1907 Nov. (Box Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "O-R" to George T. Wickes, 1907 Jan. -Sept. (Box Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M-W", incl W. L. Alley, 1906 Aug. -1907 Sept. (Box Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "W-Y" to Wickes, 1906 Oct. -1907 Sept. (Box Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous letters "K-W", incl. R. H. Teaford, to H. G. Merry, 1894 Feb. -1896 Nov. (Box Box 3)
  - M. Erskine Miller, Thurmond Coal, et. al, 1895 Jan. -1896 April (Box Box 3)
  - M. Erskine Miller, Thurmond Coal, et. al to H. G. Merry, 1893 Jan. -1894 Dec. (Box Box 3)
  - Thomas A. Mack to H. G. Merry, 1895 Jan. -Dec.; (4 folders) (Box Box 4)
  - Moody, Carpenter & Co. to H. G. Merry, 1891 March -1895 Feb. (Box Box 4)
  - M. Erskine Miller to H. G. Merry, 1893 Feb. -1894 Nov. (Box Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M-Mo" to H. G. Merry, 1891 -1897 (Box Box 4)
  - H. R. Durkee to E. C. Means, 1904 Sept. -1905 April (Box Box 4)
  - Walter Wallingford & Co. to E. C. Means, 1904 Sept. -1905 July; (2 folders) (Box Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B-R" to Merry, Means, 1895 -1905 (Box Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ca-Ce", 1897 April -1901 July (Box Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ch-Ci", 1900 -1901 (Box Box 5)
  - M. A. Hanna & Co., 1918 Jan. -1920 Feb. (Box Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-J", "K-Q", "R-Z" to F. U. Humbert, 1917 Feb. -1920 Feb.; (3 folders) (Box Box 5)
  - C. & O. Railroad to Low Moor, 1899 Aug. -1900 Dec.; (3 folders) (Box Box 5)
  - C. & O. Railroad to E. C. Means, 1901 Jan. -April (Box Box 5)
  - E. C. Means, 1901 May -July (Box Box 5)
  - C. & O. Coal Assoc. to Merry, Means, 1900 March -1901 July (Box Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous letters to Merry, Means, 1899 -1901 (Box Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "La-Le", 1902 -1903 (Box Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Lib-Lin", 1902 -1903 (Box Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Loe-Luk", 1902 -1903 (Box Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Luk-Lun", 1902 -1903 (Box Box 6)
  - Lynchburg Plow Co., 1902 -1903; (2 folders) (Box Box 6)
  - Lynn, 1903 (Box Box 6)
  - Lyman, 1902 April -1903; (2 folders) (Box Box 6)
  - U.S. Fuel Administration, Byrd; information on fuel problems during WWI, 1918 June -Sept. (Box Box 6A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "La-Lim", 1917 -1918 (Box Box 6A)
  - Dalton, Treasurer, 1918 March -May (Box Box 6A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "K", 1918 (Box Box 6A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ho-Hu", 1918 (Box Box 6A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Gar-Gla", 1917 -1918 (Box Box 6A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Gle-Gur", 1917 -1918 (Box Box 6A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Hal-Har", 1918 (Box Box 6A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C-K", 1917 -1918 (Box Box 6A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "S", 1901 -1902 (Box Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "O", 1900 -1902 (Box Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "N", 1900 -1902; (3 folders) (Box Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "J", 1904 -1906 (Box Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "F", 1901 -1904 (Box Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "H", 1899 -1900; (2 folders) (Box Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C", 1889 -1902; (2 folders) (Box Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "H", 1890 (Box Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "G", 1890 (Box Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "F", 1890 (Box Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "D", 1890 (Box Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "S", 1904 -1906 (Box Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "W", 1905 -1906 (Box Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A", 1890 (Box Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B", 1890 (Box Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, incl. Low Moor Iron Co.; Empire Rubber Co.; Robert Parrish - Attorney-at-Law; Berlingame Bros.; Hathaway & Peters, 1895 -1919 (Box Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Lea-Lob" to Cargill, 1909 -1914 (Box Box 9)
  - John H. McGowan correspondence, 1907 June -1913 April (Box Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Mar-Mee" to Cargill, 1907 -1914 (Box Box 9)
  - Cargill from Metallic, 1910 -1912; (2 folders) (Box Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Mic-Mil", 1909 -1912 (Box Box 9)
  - Michelin, 1909 -1912 (Box Box 9)
  - F. E. Cash, 1912 Jan. (Box Box 9)
  - Carson to Cargill, 1907 -1912 (Box Box 9)
  - McKee to Wilkinson, 1910 -1912 (Box Box 9)
  - McNair to Cargill, 1912 (Box Box 9)
  - Carnegie Steel Co. to Cargill, 1910 Jan. -1914 Jan. (Box Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Mey-Mil" to Cargill, 1909 -1913 (Box Box 9)
  - Miami Cycle & Mfg. Co. to Cargill, 1911 Sept. (Box Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Mill-Milt" to Cargill, 1907 -1912 (Box Box 9)
  - Mesta Machine Co. to Cargill, 1913 Dec. (Box Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Mes-Met" to Cargill, 1910 -1911 (Box Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Merc-Met" to Cargill, 1907 Jan. -1913 Dec. (Box Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Can-Cap" to Cargill, 1910 -1914 (Box Box 9A)
  - Canton to Cargill, 1908 -1912 (Box Box 9A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Cam-Can" to Cargill, 1910 -1914 (Box Box 9A)
  - Cameron Stove Co. to Cargill, 1909 Jan. -1910 (Box Box 9A)
  - Chapman Iron, Coal & Coke to Cargill, 1905 May -July (Box Box 9A)
  - Charleston Electric Supply Co. to Cargill, 1909 -1911 (Box Box 9A)
  - Charleston Mine & Supply Co. to Cargill, 1907 -1912 (Box Box 9A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Car-Cas" to Cargill, 1912 -1913 (Box Box 9A)
  - Cataract to Cargill, 1910 -1912 (Box Box 9A)
  - Meehan to Cargill, 1909 June -1910 March (Box Box 9A)
  - Catlett to Cargill, 1909 -1914 (Box Box 9A)
  - C. C. Mentz to Cargill, 1910 March -Dec. (Box Box 9A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Mas-May" to Cargill, 1912 -1913 (Box Box 9A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Cau-Cen" to Cargill, 1911 -1914 (Box Box 9A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Dom", 1916 Nov. (Box Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Dai-Dre", 1917 -1919 (Box Box 10)
  - Enlisted men to Humbert, 1918 June -1919 May (Box Box 10)
  - C. E. Bertie, 1920 -1921 (Box Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ta-Tw", 1920 Jan. -1921 Sept. (Box Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Cam-Cur", 1917 -1920 (Box Box 10)
  - Store, 1916 -1918 (Box Box 10)
  - C. & O. Railroad, 1917 -1921 (Box Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "La-Ly", 1920 -1921 (Box Box 10)
  - C. C. Cooke (Kay Moor), 1918 Jan. -Sept. (Box Box 10A)
  - Kay Moor, incl. information on geological makeup of ground beneath Low Moor; 2 newspaper articles on mine union activity, 1917 -1920 March; (4 folders) (Box Box 10A)
  - Eaton, Rhodes & Co., 1916 Sept. -1921 April (Box Box 10A)
  - General Electric to Lipscomb, 1917 Nov. -Dec. (Box Box 11)
  - Glade Coal Works to Cargill, 1911 Sept. -1912 Aug. (Box Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "For-Fud" to Lipscomb, 1918 (Box Box 11)
  - J. C. Fowle, 1899 May -Oct., 1900 Jan., Sept., Oct. (Box Box 11)
  - C. & O. Railroad to G. M. Humbert, 1925 (Box Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Cap" to Means, 1904 Sept. -Oct. (Box Box 11)
  - Walter Wallingford to Means, 1907 March (Box Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Web-Wee" to Means, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Had-Ham" to Means, 1901 -1903 (Box Box 11A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Han" to Means, 1900 -1902 (Box Box 11A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Harb-Harr" to Means, 1901 -1903 (Box Box 11A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Hart-Haw" to Means, 1901 -1903 (Box Box 11A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Has-Haz" to Means, 1900 -1903 (Box Box 11A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Hea-Hel" to Means, 1900 -1903 (Box Box 11A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Hen" to Means, 1900 -1903 (Box Box 11A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Her-Hex" to Means, 1900 -1903 (Box Box 11A)
  - Harbison & Walker Co. to Means, 1897 -1903 (Box Box 11A)
  - Harbison-Walker Refractories Co. to Cargill, 1908 April -1913 Oct. (Box Box 11A)
  - Halter to Cargill, 1911 May -1913 May (Box Box 11A)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ra-Rey" to Merry, Means, 1900 -1901 (Box Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Rh-Riv" to Merry, Means, Cargill, 1899 -1901 (Box Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Roa-Ru" to Means, 1900 -1901 (Box Box 12)
  - Frank C. Roberts to Means, 1901 March -Oct. (Box Box 12)
  - Frank C. Roberts to Merry, 1899 -1900 (Box Box 12)
  - Dalton, Nash to Means, 1902 Oct. -1903 April; (6 folders) (Box Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Dun-Dur" to Means, 1902 Nov. -1903 April (Box Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Dal-Doy" to Means, 1901 -1903 (Box Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ac-Ai" to Means, 1903 (Box Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Al" to Means, 1903 (Box Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ab-Au" to Means, 1904 Jan. -April (Box Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "American" to Means, 1903 (Box Box 13)
  - Walter Wallingford to Means, 1905 Jan. -June; (6 folders) (Box Box 13)
  - Thomas A. Mack to Merry, 1896 July -1897 Feb.; (2 folders) (Box Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Smi-Som" to Means, 1901 -1904 (Box Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Sou-Sq" to Means, 1901 -1904 (Box Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Sta" to Means, 1901 -1904 (Box Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ste-Sto" to Means, 1901 -1904 (Box Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Str" to Means, 1901 -1904 (Box Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Stu-Sy" to Means, 1901 -1904 (Box Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Sag-Sam,T'' to Fowle, 1899 Sept. -1900 April (Box Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1894 -1902 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ad-Au" to Merry, 1888 -1889 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "B" to Merry, 1888 -1889 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ca-Cr" to Merry, 1888 -1889 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "D" to Merry, 1888 -1889 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ma" to Merry, 1895 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Y-Z" to Cargill, 1906 (Box Box 15)
  - Gaines & Co to Merry, 1895 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "O" to Merry, 1901 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Hi-Hu" to J. C. Fowle, 1889 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C-D, S-W" to J. C. Fowle, 1900 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "L-Y" to J. C. Fowle, 1893 -1894 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "D-R" to J. C. Fowle, 1893 -1894 (Box Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "A-C" to J. C. Fowle, 1893 -1894 (Box Box 15)
  - Kay Moor titles, John Wehrle, A. W. Hamilton, 1924 (Box Box 16)
  - South Tent & Awning Co., 1915 June -July (Box Box 16)
  - South Side Foundry & Machine Works to P. A. Croxton, 1915 Sept. -1916 June (Box Box 16)
  - Southern Railway Supply Co., 1915 (Box Box 16)
  - H. M. Smith to Croxton, 1915 Oct. -1916 July (Box Box 16)
  - Tarver Bros. Stationary to Croxton, 1916 April (Box Box 16)
  - Tribune Printing Co. to Croxton, 1916 April (Box Box 16)
  - Tredegar Iron Works to Croxton, 1915 July -1916 July (Box Box 16)
  - C. A. Turner to Croxton, 1915 Aug. -1916 July (Box Box 16)
  - Waterburg Co. to Croxton, 1915 July -1916 June (Box Box 16)
  - Western Electric Co. to Croxton, 1914 July -1916 Aug. (Box Box 16)
  - Westinghouse Electric & Mfg. Co. to Croxton, 1915 Dec. -1916 July (Box Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Pa-Pr" to Lipscomb, 1917 Nov. -Dec. (Box Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Pr-Pu" to Lipscomb, 1918 (Box Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Q" to Lipscomb, 1918 (Box Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ra-Ru" to Lipscomb, 1917 Dec. -1918 (Box Box 16)
  - E. M. Cabell to Monteith, 1918 Dec. -1919 Oct.; (3 folders) (Box Box 17)
  - E. M. Cabell to Lipscomb, assistant treasurer, 1918 Jan. -April (Box Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ae-As" to Lipscomb, ass't. treasurer, 1918 March -Dec. (Box Box 17)
  - C. & O. Railroad loss and damage claims to Croxton, 1915 Dec. -1918 Dec. (Box Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ca, Ch" to Lipscomb, 1918 (Box Box 17)
  - Baughman - orders, to Croxton, 1916 (Box Box 17A)